http://www.threestooges.com/terms-and-conditions#privacy

April Shorts
What’s The Matador?
Feature Films
The Three Stooges Movie (2012)
June Shorts
Guns a Poppin!
June Shorts
Spooks!
March Shorts
Who Done It?
September Shorts
Wham-Bam-Slam!
September Shorts
Gents Without Cents – “Niagara Falls!”
Filmography
The Three Stooges Movie (2012)
Moe Howard
Happy Birthday Moe!
Bios
Happy Birthday Moe!
Stooge News
Happy Birthday Curly Joe!
New Hit It Rich! Casino Slots featuring The...
The Three Stooges Premium Coffee
Elevate Your Fandom With All-New Stooge Gear
Time Life Releases “The Best of The Three...
Home
Terms & Conditions
Terms & Conditions
TERMS OF USE
Please read these Terms Of Use carefully before using this site. By using this site, you signify your agreement with these Terms Of Use. If you do not agree with any of the below Terms Of Use, do not use this site. C3 Entertainment, Inc. reserves the right, in its sole discretion to modify, alter or otherwise update these Terms Of Use at any time and you agree to be bound by such modifications, alterations or updates.
TRADEMARKS, COPYRIGHTS AND RESTRICTIONS
This site is controlled and operated by C3 Entertainment, Inc., 1415 Gardena Ave., Glendale, CA 91204. The telephone number is (818) 956-1337. All material on this site, including, but not limited to images, illustrations, audio clips, and video clips, is protected by copyrights which are owned and controlled by C3 Entertainment, Inc. or by other parties that have licensed their material to C3 Entertainment, Inc. (‘Copyrights’). Material from threestooges.com or any web site owned, operated, licensed or controlled by C3 Entertainment, Inc. may not be copied, reproduced, republished, uploaded, posted, transmitted, or distributed in any way. Modification of the materials or use of the materials for any other purpose is a violation of the copyrights and other proprietary rights. For purposes of this Terms Of Use Agreement, the use of any such material on any other web site or networked computer environment is prohibited.
PRIVACY
C3 Entertainment, Inc. is very respectful about the privacy concerns of the visitors to its sites on the Internet. As a general policy, no personal information is automatically collected from visitors to its sites. However, certain non-personal information of visitors is recorded by the standard operation of C3 Entertainment, Inc.’s Internet servers. This information is primarily used to provide an enhanced online experience for the visitor. Information tracked includes the type of browser being used by the visitor (e.g., Netscape, Internet Explorer), the type of operating system (e.g., Macintosh, Windows) in use by the visitor and the domain name of the visitor’s Internet service provider (e.g., America Online, Earthlink). By having this information, web pages optimized for a particular visitor’s computer is automatically available to that visitor. Other uses of this information include internal review of the number of visitors to the sites but only in an aggregate and non-personally-identifiable form, E-mail addresses and other personally identifiable data about visitors to this site are known to C3 Entertainment, Inc. only when voluntarily submitted.
Personally identifiable information that may be collected in connection with visitors voluntarily filling out contest entry forms or subscribing to newsletters is retained by C3 Entertainment, Inc. and not sold or otherwise transferred outside the company. This information is used to better understand visitors= use of our sites and to support transactions made on the sites.
However, this data in an aggregate form may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising or other uses. We sometimes also use e-mail addresses and other personally identifiable information to contact visitors who communicate with us. For example, we direct e-mail to visitors who provide us with their e-mail addresses for specific purposes such as receiving our e-mail newsletters or being notified if they have won one of our contests.
Many of the C3 Entertainment, Inc. web sites, including this one, place a ‘cookie’ in the browser file of a C3 Entertainment, Inc. user’s computer. The cookie itself does not contain any personally identifying information. Although the cookie could enable C3 Entertainment, Inc. to relate a user’s use of a C3 Entertainment, Inc. site to information that the user has specifically and knowingly provided, C3 Entertainment, Inc. does not do so for any kids’ sites.
Users should be aware that when they voluntarily disclose personal information (e.g., user name, e-mail address, telephone number) on the bulletin boards or in the chat areas, that information can be collected and used by others and may result in unsolicited messages from other people.
To the extent that any of our sites accessible through C3 Entertainment, Inc. has additional practices, these practices will be explained at that site.
A SPECIAL NOTE FOR PARENTS CONCERNING PRIVACY
On sites specifically designed for children, C3 Entertainment, Inc. makes a special effort to encourage children to consult with their parents before furnishing data. However, C3 Entertainment, Inc. believes that parents should supervise their children’s online activities and consider using parental control tools available from online services and software manufacturers that help provide a kid-friendly online environment. These tools can also prevent children from disclosing online their name, address, and other personal information without parental permission. For additional information about parental control tools, please consult the ‘Consumer Assistance’ page of the Direct Marketing Association home page (www.the-dma.org).
LINKED SITES
C3 Entertainment, Inc., whether or not affiliated with sites which may be linked to this site, is not responsible for their content (‘Linked Sites’). The Linked Sites are for your convenience only and you access them at your own risk.
DISCLAIMER
The materials in C3 Entertainment, Inc.’s Web Sites are provided ‘as is’ and without warranties of any kind either express or implied. To the fullest extent permissible pursuant to applicable law, C3 Entertainment, Inc. disclaims all warranties, express or implied, including, but not limited to, implied warranties of merchantability and fitness for a particular purpose. C3 Entertainment, Inc. does not warrant that the functions contained in the materials will be uninterrupted or error-free, that defects will be corrected, or that C3 Entertainment, Inc.’s web sites or the server that makes them available are free of viruses or other harmful components. C3 Entertainment, Inc. does not warrant or make any representations regarding the use or the results of the use of the materials in C3 Entertainment, Inc.’s web sites in terms of their correctness, accuracy, reliability, or otherwise. You (and not C3 Entertainment, Inc.) assume the entire cost of all necessary servicing, repair or correction. Applicable law may not allow the exclusion of implied warranties, so the above exclusion may not apply to you. The material that you read in C3 Entertainment, Inc.’s web sites is provided solely for entertainment and promotional purposes. The information and opinions expressed in Bulletin Boards, Chat Rooms, or other forums conducted on this site (‘Forums’) are not necessarily those of C3 Entertainment, Inc. or its affiliated or related entities or content providers and C3 Entertainment, Inc. makes no representations or warranties regarding that information or those opinions. Furthermore, neither C3 Entertainment, Inc. nor its affiliated or related entities or its content providers are responsible or liable to any person or entity whatsoever (including, without limitation, persons who may use or rely on such data/materials or to whom such data/materials may be furnished) for any loss, damage (whether actual, consequential, punitive or otherwise), injury, claim, liability or other cause of any kind or character whatsoever based upon or resulting from any information or opinions provided in C3 Entertainment, Inc.’s web sites.
SUBMISSIONS
Any notes, message/billboard postings, ideas, suggestions, concepts or other material submitted will become the property of C3 Entertainment, Inc. throughout the universe and C3 Entertainment, Inc. shall be entitled to use the material for any type of use forever including in any media whether now known or hereafter devised. When you submit material to C3 Entertainment, Inc.’s web sites, you agree that C3 Entertainment, Inc. has the right to publish the material for any type of use as online above including promotional and advertising purposes.
C3 Entertainment, Inc. is not responsible for any material posted on our Forums. You shall not submit or otherwise publish through such Forums any content which:
libels, defames, invades privacy, or is obscene, pornographic, abusive, or threatening;
infringes any intellectual property or other right of any entity or person including, but not limited to violating anyone’s copyrights or trademarks;
violates any law;
advocates illegal activity;
advertises or otherwise solicits funds or is a solicitation for goods or services (collectively ‘Non-Approved Material’).
You agree to indemnity C3 Entertainment, Inc. and its officers, directors, employees, agents, distributors and affiliates from and against any and all third party claims, demands, liabilities, costs, or expenses, including reasonable attorney’s fees, resulting from your breach of any of the foregoing agreements, representations, and warranties.
E-MAIL AND POSTINGS RECEIVED
Do not post any threatening or libelous e-mails or material on this site that would be considered a violation of any law. C3 Entertainment, Inc. will fully cooperate with any law enforcement authorities or court order requesting or directing C3 Entertainment, Inc. to disclose the identity of anyone posting any such e-mails or materials.
JURISDICTIONAL ISSUES
Unless otherwise specified, the materials in C3 Entertainment, Inc. web sites are presented solely for the purpose of entertainment and promoting programs, films and other products available in the United States, its territories, possessions, and protectorates. This site is controlled and operated by C3 Entertainment, Inc. from its offices within the State of California, United States of America. C3 Entertainment, Inc. makes no representation that materials in C3 Entertainment, Inc.’s web sites are appropriate or available for use in other locations. Those who choose to access this site from other locations do so on their own initiative and are responsible for compliance with local laws, if and to the extent local laws are applicable.
This agreement shall be governed by, construed and enforced in accordance with the laws of the State of California, as it is applied to agreements entered into and to be performed entirely within such State. Any action you, any third party of C3 Entertainment, Inc. bring to enforce this agreement or, in connection with, any matters related to this site shall be brought only in either the state or Federal Courts located in Los Angeles County, California, and you expressly consent to the jurisdiction of said courts. If any provision of this agreement shall be unlawful, void, or for any reason unenforceable, then that provision shall be deemed severable from this agreement and shall not affect the validity and enforceability of any remaining provisions. This is the entire agreement between the parties relating to the matters contained herein and shall not be modified except in writing, signed by C3 Entertainment, Inc.
Share
Facebook
Twitter
Google +
Pinterest
Search
Sign Up For The Three Stooges & ShopknucKleheads Email List & Save 10% on Your Next Order
Subscribe To The Three Stooges & Shopknuckleheads List and save 10%
Who Done It?
Happy Birthday Curly Joe!
July 10, 2020
Top 10 Three Stooges Summer Shorts!
March 17, 2020
New Hit It Rich! Casino Slots featuring The Boys!
January 21, 2020
Check out the new Three Stooges store at amazon.com/thethreestooges
This site uses cookies:
Find out more.Okay, thanks
